■
本字幕由 YYeTs人人影视 翻译制作
更多美剧更新 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
《反恐24小时》前情提要
Previously on 24.
没有你  桑加拉就没有了领袖
Without you,Sangala has no leader.
这些人为杜巴库卖命  对吗
These people,they work for Dubaku,don't they?
马托波先生
Mr. Matobo,
我们已经控制藏身处的通风口
we've accessed the air intake to your safe room.
现在正释放双硬脂铵气体
We are feeding in ammonium dysterate gas.
若不开门  你将必死无疑
If you do not open the door,you will die.
乌勒
Ule...
带他出来  还有这个女人
Get him out of there! Get the woman,too.
-泰勒先生  -萨姆
- Mr. Taylor.  - Sam.
我不能久留
I can't stay long.
他们杀了罗杰并伪造成是自杀
They killed Roger and made it look like a suicide.
我不知道具体是谁
I don't know who they are.
他们只说要是我泄露半个字就会杀我灭口
They just said that they would kill me if I said anything.
罗杰被任命去审计部门内部的经纪人
Roger was tasked with auditing the brokers
资料都在这里
in his department. It's all here.
银行账号
Account numbers,
交易记录  他掌握的所有情报都有
trading records,everything that he knew.
罗杰当时正调查他不该调查的事
Roger was looking into things he shouldn't have.
是你杀了我儿子
You killed my son.
先生  这是呔哩锭锌
It's tetradyzine,sir.
这是神经肌肉麻醉剂
It's a neuromuscular paralytic.
一切尽在掌握之中
The situation here is in control.
-你在跟踪洛斯小姐吗  -对
- Are you tracking Ms. Roth? - Yeah.
是时候把她带回自己公寓了
Time to get her back to her apartment.
-洛斯小姐  -怎么了
-Ms. Roth.  -Yes?
亨利·泰勒派我来
Henry Taylor sent me.
泰勒先生一直在调查你提供的线索
Mr. Taylor's been looking into the matter you discussed.
你处境危险
He believes you're in imminent danger.
他让我为你提供保护性监护
He wants me to place you in protective custody.
拉里  我是蕾妮  我看到他们
Larry,it's Renee. I've got a visual on them
正把马托波和他妻子送上卡车
loading Matobo and his wife into a truck. Where the hell
-特警组怎么还没来  -他们还得五分钟
-is SWAT? - They're still about five minutes out.
把枪给我
Drop the gun.
据我了解  她单枪匹马来的
Far as I can tell,she's alone.
该死  鲍尔  你这狗娘养的杂种
Damn you,Bauer,you son of a bitch.
尼科尔斯要我们和马托波会合前
Nichols wants her out of the way
在路上就把她做了
before we deliver Matobo.
杀了她
Kill her.
好
Yeah.
转过身
Turn around.
相信我  我能保住你的命
If you trust me. I'll get you through this alive.
以下事件发生在下午一点到两点
The following takes place betweem 1 p.m. and 2 p.m.
我要再派三个小队搜寻
I want three more teams combing the site
马托波被绑架的地方
where Matobo was abducted.
不得已的话  可以从地方上抽调人员
Pull them in from regional if you have to.
我们要增加搜寻范围
We're going to expand the search.
和地铁警员合作并建立一个
Coordinate with metro police to set up a point-by-point grid
以十英里为半径的点对点网络
encompassing a ten-mile radius.
连线国安局
And talk with NSA.
我想让所有这些搜查
I want to back all of this up
都有卫星同步扫描支援
with synchronized satellite sweeps.
-我会尽力  -什么意思
- I'll do what I can. - What does that mean?
每次我需要什么  他们都会瞎扯些
Well,every time I ask for something,they pull their
事关机密之类的屁话搪塞
cloak-and-dagger nonsense.
于是我不得不求爷爷告奶奶地申请
I have to get approval
只为了每次获得那一丁点的小资料
for every little scrap of data.
詹尼斯  这对谁来说都不容易
Janis,this isn't easy for anybody.
拜托了
Just,please,
请努力尝试
make it happen.
是  长官
Yes,sir.
下一场袭击已迫在眉睫
We know that another attack could be imminent.
唯一阻止它的办法是找到阿尔梅达和鲍尔
The only way to stop it is to find Almeida and Bauer
并拿到CIP装置
and take control of the CIP device.
可能有人还不知道  我跟你们说
Um... for those of you who haven't heard,
蕾妮被这些人绑架
Renee Walker was abducted by these people.
我们是她的最后一线希望
We're the only chance she's got.
所以  我们回去继续工作
So,let's get to work.
有什么进展
What have you got?
音频分析室剔除了录音中的杂音
Audio forensics cleaned up the recording.
好
Okay.
沃克已经没有利用价值
Walker is extraneous.
你到我这里之前做了她
Kill her before you get here.
好  我们很快会和你会合
Okay,we'll be with you soon.
手脚麻利点
Be quick about it.
与马托波总理较量让杜巴库感到焦虑
Dubaku's anxious to get his hands on the prime minister.
好好分析这段录音  找到他们
Been combing through it,looking for a tag
泄露出来的地点
that will give up their location.
-目前为止还一无所获  -还有谁
- So far,nothing. - Is there anybody else
能来帮你忙
you can put on this?
拉里  不值得这样
Larry,I don't think it's worth it.
-这里面没什么情报了  -好吧
- There's nothing here. - All right.
好吧  去帮詹尼斯忙国安局的事
Fine,help Janis coordinate with NSA.
拉里  对于蕾妮的事  我感到很遗憾
I'm sorry about Renee,Larry.
她是个出色的探员
She was a good agent.
她还生死未卜
We don't know that she's dead yet!
-明白吗  -明白
- All right? - All right
你确定就在这里吗
Are you sure this is it?
她会缺氧窒息
She's going to run out of air.
托尼说她就在挖土机旁边
Tony said near the backhoe.
这里  在这里
Here,here.
找到了  克罗伊  找到她了
I got her,Chloe. I got her.
好的  她在这里  就在这里
All right,here she is. Here she is.
没呼吸了  给我肾上腺素
She's not breathing. Give me the adrenaline.
没事的
It's all right.
你没事  你没事
You're okay... you're okay.
你们是谁
Who are you?
杰克的同事
We're working with Jack.
他让我们到这里来找你
He told us where to find you.
你会好的
It's gonna be okay.
深呼吸  你会没事的
Take deep breaths. You're gonna be okay.
我们快到约定地点了
We're close to the rendezvous point.
你还有多久能到
What's your eta?
好
Good.
一会见
We'll see you then.
都安排好了
It's all set.
尼科尔斯正带着钻石赶过来
Nichols is on his way with the diamonds.
杰克  你是不是有心事
Is something bothering you,Jack?
不  我在想
No,I was wondering...
你干嘛不告诉托尼你是怎么把他弄出反恐组的
why you never told Tony how you got him out of CTU.
你是怎么做到的
How did you do it?
克里斯多佛·安德森
Christopher Anderson.
克里斯多佛·安德森当时想杀他
Christopher Anderson tried to kill him.
安德森没想杀托尼
Anderson had no intention of killing Tony.
他给他注射的时候故意没扎进动脉
He purposely missed the artery when he injected him.
这样刚好足以放慢他的心跳
It was just enough to slow his heart
让人以为他已经死了
to the point where you'd think that he was dead.
我的任务是  把他抢救回来
My job was to...extract and revive him and...
利用他来对付你
use him against you.
然后呢
And?
等到他的生命体征稳定时
By the time I stabilized him,
你已经杀了安德森
you had already killed Anderson.
任务失败
Mission had failed.
于是我们销声匿迹
So,my team went dark.
他为何不放托尼走
Why did he just let Tony go?
托尼自愿留下的
Tony chose to stay with us.
他心中充满了仇恨的怒火
He was consumed with hatred and anger
因米歇尔之死怀恨政府
over what the government had done to Michelle.
不管怎样  我找他谈了谈
Anyway... I talked to him.
更重要的是  我听他倾诉
More importantly,I listened to him.
很快  我们便一致认为
Pretty soon,we came to realize that...
我的想法是对的
I was right.
什么想法
About what?
行事规则已经改变
That the rules had changed.
连荣誉也消失殆尽
And there was nothing such as honor left.
我们必须相互扶持
That we would have to take care of each other.
情同手足
Like brothers.
爱默生先生
Mr. Emerson.
什么事
Yeah?
快到了
We're almost there.
我们如何交易
How is the deal gonna go down?
别担心  杰克  你马上就会知道
Don't worry,Jack. You're about to find out.
准备好了吗
Are you ready?
好了
Yeah.
你确定
Are you sure?
是的
Yeah.
你去和利特法克把守大门
Go help Litvak with the door.
-把马托波夫妇带出来  -好的
-Go get the Matobos. -Yeah.
你最好告诉我  这到底是怎么回事
You better tell me what the hell's going on.
放下枪  戴维
Drop the gun,David.
我不知道你想干什么
You know,I just couldn't figure out your play,
所以我给你时间  让你说清楚
so I tried to give you some time so you'd come clean,
因为我们亲如兄弟  对吧  托尼
'cause we are like brothers,right,Tony?
把枪放下  戴维
Put the gun down,David.
你真以为我会让你
You actually think that I would let you
抢走我的钻石吗
steal those diamonds from me?
与钻石无关
It's not about the diamonds.
而是残杀无辜的生命
It's about killing innocent people.
我必须阻止你
I can't let you finish this.
开枪
Take a shot.
放下武器  否则我杀了他
Put down the weapon or I will kill him.
托尼  开枪
Tony,take a shot!
-闭嘴  杰克  -放下枪  托尼
- Shut up,Jack!  - Put it down,Tony,
-否则我杀了他  -戴维  我不想杀你
- Or he's dead.  - David,I don't want to kill you,
-但我不会手软  -去死吧  托尼
- but I will.  - Damn it,Tony,
放下
Drop the...
你没事吧
You okay?
没事
Yeah.
戴维
David.
你说鲍尔和阿尔梅达
Okay,you say that Bauer and Almeida
都是卧底  可是反恐小组已经被撤销了
are working undercover,but CTU has been shut down,
如果你说的属实
So,I mean,if you're telling the truth,
这项行动由谁主持
who's running this operation?
我们
We are.
我们独自行动
We're not working with any agency.
我们认为多处国家机关
We believe there's been widespread infiltration of the
被杜巴库和朱玛政权收买
government by Dubaku and the Juma regime.
好吧
Okay.
我要联系我的上司
I need to contact my boss.
-告诉他我平安无事  -不行
- He needs to know that I'm okay. - You can't do that.
为什么
Why not?
杜巴库在联调局内有眼线
Dubaku has informants in the FBI.
如果他们得知你还活着
If they find out you're alive,
他们就会发现杰克的敌对身份
They'll know Jack is working against them.
你不知道能相信谁
You don't know who you can trust.
我相信莫斯探员
I can trust agent Moss.
你没听明白吗
You're not listening to me.
你不能联系联调局
You cannot contact the FBI.
那会威胁到本次行动
You will jeopardize this operation,
我不会允许的
and I won't let you do that.
你不是我上司  拉里才是
Well,I don't work for you; I work for Larry.
把电话给我
Now give me a phone.
拜托你坐着别动
Sit still,please.
行动接近尾声了
We're nearing the endgame.
杜巴库是关键人物
Dubaku is the key
我们能通过他找出政府内的腐败官员
to finding out who in the government has been corrupted.
幸运的是  我们手上有他想要的
Luckily,we have something he wants.
马托波
Matobo.
这是找到杜巴库的绝佳机会
He's our best chance to locate Dubaku,
我们能够夺回CIP模块
reacquire the CIP module
挖出政府内的贪官污吏
and get to the bottom of the government corruption.
一切结束之前  你不能活过来
Until all that happens,you have to stay dead.
是我
Yeah.
找到沃克探员了吗
Did you find agent Walker?
找到了  杰克
Yeah,we got her,Jack.
她没事  你在哪
She's fine. Where are you?
北林机场
Northwoods Airfield.
利特法克死了  爱默生受伤
Litvak is dead. Emerson's been wounded.
尼科尔斯在途中  你得马上过来
Nichols is en route. I need you to get over here now.
你跟马托波谈过了吗
Have you talked to Matobo?
-还没  -必须征得他的同意  杰克
- Not yet. - He needs to agree to this,Jack.
没有他  这事儿成不了
We can't do it without him.
我会让他同意的  你尽快过来
I'll get him to agree. Just get over here.
没事的
It's all right.
究竟怎么回事
What the hell is going on?
马托波先生  我不会伤害你们夫妇
Mr. Matobo,I'm not going to hurt you or your wife.
我知道你们很害怕
I know how scared you are
我也了解你们的遭遇
and I know what you've been through,
我们是来帮你的
But we are here to help you.
上天啊  你在说什么
What in god's name are you talking about?
你绑架了我们
You kidnapped us.
我们必须取得杜巴库的信任
We had to to gain Dubaku's trust.
那是我们要找的人  我们正在试图阻止他
That's the man we're after. We're trying to stop him.
我要联系我的人
I want to call my people.
在我没有解释清楚前不能让你这么做
I can't let you do that,not until you hear me out.
我们有个计划可以阻止杜巴库
Sir,we have a plan to stop dubaku,
但是我们需要你的帮助
but we can't do it without your help.
我们时间不多了
We don't have much time.
求你了
Please.
帮帮我们
Come with me.
杜巴库先生
Mr. Dubaku.
我准备去见面地点
I'm heading to the meeting place.
他们正带马托波过来
They're bringing matobo now.
和他老婆
And his wife?
他们俩一起
Both of them.
你见到马托波后  就知道该做什么了
Once you have Matobo,you know what to do.
爱默生的小队已没什么价值了  解决他们
Emerson's team is now a loose end.Tie it off.
你确定么
Are you sure about this?
我们可能还要他们效力
We may need their services again.
我宁愿节约我的钻石
I would rather keep my diamonds,
阿尔梅达已证明他的立场了
and Almeida has proved to be a liability.
那么
So.
白宫有消息么
Any response from the white house?
不是我们想要的
Not the one we wanted.
美军还在原地
American forces are still in position.
必须让泰勒总统知道我们抓了马托波
President taylor must know we have Matobo.
她没马托波不能攻击桑格拉
She can't attack Sangala without him.
政府会崩溃的
The country will collapse.
泰勒可能拖延时间
Taylor may be holding out hope that she can
来想办法拯救马托波
somehow retrieve Matobo.
要么她不相信
Or she doesn't believe
我们得给她点威胁
we are willing to carry out our threats.
她只会在美国人死了后才能有反应
She will only respond when there are dead Americans.
我见到马托波的时候给你电话
I'll call you when I have Matobo.
这些人会听候你的吩咐
These gentlemen are at your command.
还有1300架飞机在飞行
There are still 1,300 planes in the air.
那个地点你想攻击
Which region do you want targeted?
华盛顿特区
Washington,DC.
好的
Yeah.
我明白  鲍勃
I understand,Bob.
好的  谢谢
All right,thanks.
刚才是国家安全局的鲍勃·康奈尔
That was Bob Cornell at NSA.
他们查到另外一个防火墙缺口
They've detected another firewall breach.
又有一次攻击
There's been another attack?
还没  但他们确定CIP装置又一次启动了
Not yet,but they believe the CIP device is being utilized.
我们必须认为杜巴库开始另一次攻击
We have to assume Dubaku is initiating another attack.
确切的说这次不会只是个警告
It's safe to say this won't be another warning shot.
这次杜巴库肯定要杀人
This time Dubaku's gonna make sure that people die.
就我个人而言
I want to speak personally
全国所有紧急反映人员
with all first responders across the country.
他们必须打起精神去面对最惨的情况
They need to know to brace for the worst
我们全力支持他们
and that they have our full support.
做好最坏打算之外
Instead of preparing for it,
也许我们应该尝试
maybe we should be trying
去得到这次交锋的主动权  总统女士
to preempt this attack,madam president.
杜巴库给我们的
The deadline Dubaku gave us
从桑格拉撤军的底线已经过了
for withdrawing our troops from Sangala has passed,
但我们可以做点姿态
But if we made some kind of gesture...
开始紧急后撤
began an immediate pullback,
也许会让杜巴库暂时停止攻击
It might keep Dubaku from pulling the trigger.
我们讨论过这个  伊桑  这是不可能的
We've discussed this,Ethan.It's not an option.
我不会听命于这个疯子的
I won't be dictated to by this madman.
总统女士  没马托波我们不可以侵入桑格拉
Madam president,we can't invade Sangala without Matobo,
而他获救的可能性很小
And there's very little chance of him being recovered.
我们为什么要拿国民的生命冒险
Why are we risking American lives?
我已经说了我的理由了
I've told you my reasons.
后撤我们的队伍还不算迟
Withdraw our forces before it's too late.
你让我当顾问是因为你相信我的意见
You asked me to be your advisor because you trust
现在就是我的意见
my opinion. Well,I'm giving it to you now.
我们别无选择
We're out of options.
不是的  伊桑
We're not,Ethan.
国家安全局正在搜索
The NSA is attempting to localize
可能被攻击的区域
what part of the infrastructure is being targeted,
联邦调查局正在寻找CIP设备
And the FBI is still trying to track down the CIP device.
我会随时和这两个部门联系
I'll keep an open channel with both agencies.
随时向你报告
I'll keep you apprised.
好的
Good.
让我看看
Let me see it.
Let me see it!
戴维  这不是为了钻石
This wasn't about the diamonds,David.
我觉得你太过分了
You crossed a line I wasn't willing to cross.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你想让我原谅
You're looking for forgiveness...
去死吧
go to hell.
你
You...
内疚去吧
live with it.
你想让我们冒生命危险
You're asking us to risk our lives
去杜巴库那里
to be delivered into Dubaku's hands,based on nothing
无凭无据  只凭你口头说说
but what you have told us.
我说的都是事实
Everything I have told you is the truth.
杜巴库在这里  我们要找出他
Dubaku is in this country,and we need to find him.
你是我们唯一的赌注
You have as much at stake as we do.
他是你我两国共同的敌人
He's attacked both our countries.
听他的  乌勒
Listen to him,Ule.
你自己告诉我  泰勒总统
You told me yourself president Taylor
在这些攻击停止前
will not commit forces to Sangala
不会派兵去桑格拉
until these attacks are stopped.
但我们怎么可以相信这个人
But how can we trust this man?
因为他没有撒谎的理由
Because he has no reason to lie.
我会按你说的做  但是只能我一个人去
I will do what you ask,but I will go alone.
杜巴库要的是你和你夫人
Dubaku wants you and your wife.
-说好的  -不行
-That's the deal. -No.
我不会把我老婆交到那个怪物的手上
I will not put my wife in the hands of that monster.
我跟你说实话  先生
I will be honest with you,sir.
他想要你妻子做交换条件
He wants your wife as leverage.
你们无论谁留下  他都会取消交易
If I don't deliver both of you,he will back out.
交换条件
Leverage.
你是说他想通过折磨她
You mean he wants to torture her
好让我告诉他我知道有哪些人在
to make me tell him what I know about the resistance
-桑加拉  -是的  先生
-in Sangala? -Yes,sir.
我们不会让他得逞
And we won't let that happen.
我们会跟在你后面
We'll be following you.
但你还是不能向我保证
Still,you can't promise me
她不受到伤害  你能吗
that she won't be harmed,can you?
你能吗
Can you?
我不会这么做的
I won't do it.
我能跟我丈夫单独谈谈吗
May I speak with my husband?
当然  夫人
Of course,ma'am.
我想这么做  乌勒
I want to do this,Ule.
-什么  -我为自己打开来
-What? -I am ashamed
避难所的门而感到丢脸
that I opened the door to the safe room.
我想做对我们国家有益的事
I want to do what is right for our country.
不是那样的
Absolutely not.
你阻止不了我  乌勒
You can't stop me,Ule.
桑加拉也是我的祖国
Sangala is my country,too.
我在你身边支持了你22年
I have been by your side for 22 years.
我不会就这么放弃的
I am not going to leave it now.
鲍尔先生  我和太太一起去
Mr. Bauer.We will do this together.
谢谢
Thank you.
你们都非常勇敢
You are both very brave.
我们现在得马上离开
We'll need to go soon.
请稍等我一下
Excuse me for one moment.
托尼
Tony.
马托波夫妇同意跟我们合作了
The Matobos are gonna work with us.
我们得走了
We've got to go.
托尼
Tony.
我们把尸体抬走吧
Let's get the bodies out of sight.
我们已经锁定了联邦航空局
We're locked onto the FAA node.
开始改变路线
Begin rerouting the targets.
RSA 471  右转  目标274
RSA 471,turn right,heading 274.
下降并保持飞行高度至270
Descend and maintain flight level 270
呼叫白宫
Call the white house.
这是国家安全局最新的报告
The latest report from the NSA.
-我可以为简单汇报一下  -说吧
-I can summarize it for you. -Go ahead.
他们还没能找出防火墙的漏洞
They've had no luck In localizing the firewall breach.
杜巴库可以袭击任何地方
Dubaku's attack could hit anywhere.
联邦调查局怎么样
What about the FBI?
他们已经派出了所有能派的探员
They've dedicated every available agent
去搜寻马托波
to the manhunt for Matobo.
他们也没有进展
They're no closer to finding him.
不好意思
Uh,excuse me.
我们走投无路了  总统女士
We're at a dead end,madam president.
你需要下令撤退
You need to order the pullback,
而且必须现在马上
and you need to order it now.
能跟踪吗
Can it be traced?
好
Okay.
稍等一下
Hold on.
-总统女士  -怎么了  蒂姆
-Madam president. -What is it,Tim?
我刚刚转接到一个电话
I've just been forwarded a scrambled call.
是杜巴库上校打来的
It's from Colonel Dubaku.
他要求跟您对话
He's demanding to speak with you.
我接
I'll take it.
我是泰勒总统
This is president Taylor.
总统女士  我很失望
Madam president... I'm disappointed
你没能认真的按照我的要求做
that you have not taken my demands seriously.
你的部队还在逼近我的国家
Your forces are still in position near my country.
杜巴库上校  我向你保证
Colonel Dubaku,I assure you we've had
我们刚刚对你的要求进行了严肃的讨论
very serious discussions regarding your demands.
现在没时间讨论了
The time for discussions is over.
你们撤军的
The deadline for your forces
时限已经过了
to begin their withdrawal has passed.
到窗户那去
Go to the window.
看看西南方  总统女士
Look to the southwest,madam president.
什么
What?
看看你都干了什么
See what you have done.
杜巴库上校  你胆敢威胁到
Colonel dubaku,if you're endangering
一个美国人的生命的话
one american life...
我的天啊
Oh,my god.
去吧  总统女士
Go,madam president.
你个狗娘养的
You son of a bitch.
一小时内照我说的做
Comply with my demands within the hour,
否则一万多美国人就会死
Or 10,000 more americans will die.
所有内阁还都在吗
Is the cabinet still assembled?
是的  总统女士
Yes,madam president.
出事的是芝加哥131航班
It was flight 131 out of chicago.
上面有240个乘客和10个机组人员
240 passengers,ten crew members.
他们和一架乘载21人的通勤
They collided with a small commuter jet
喷气式飞机相撞
carrying 21 people.
很有可能
There's also a high probability
地面也有人员伤亡
of casualties on the ground.
飞机坠毁在艾治区附近的
The aircraft went down in a residential neighborhood
居民区
near edgeborough.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们刚刚得到消息说
We've also just gotten word that
布莱顿议员和他的妻子
congressman brighton and his wife
可能在这架航班上  我们正在等待进一步确认
may have been on 131. we're waiting for confirmation.
还有多少架飞机在飞
How many planes are still in the air?
超过1300架
Over 1,300.
总统女士
Madam president,
这是危及美国生命的大灾难
This is a catastrophic loss of american lives,
而且情况只会更糟
and it's only going to get worse.
我们必须在下一个限期之前撤军
We have to withdraw our forces before the next deadline.
我不得不同意  总统阁下
I'm forced to agree,madam president.
继续说  蒂姆  我想知道你的看法
Go ahead,Tim. I want to hear what you think.
我们没有准备好应对
We're simply not prepared to contend with the scope
这些恐怖分子所能造成的大面积破坏
of damage these people can inflict.
刚才的灾难
The tragedy we've just witnessed
比起他们对电网
is nothing compared
或核设施的攻击而造成的破坏来说
to what could happen if they begin targeting
简直就是小儿科了
power grids,nuclear facilities.
我们应该考虑是否值得用成千上万美国民众的
We're talking deaths in the hundreds of thousands.
生命去支持那样的一个政策
all in support of a policy
而且这个政策的成功依赖于马托波
That cannot possibly succeed without Matobo.
他是唯一一个可以稳定桑加拉局势的人
He's the only man who can stabilize Sangala.
没有他的协助
Without him,
整个计划就不具备可行性
The entire operation is pointless.
我们仍然有一丝希望
There's still a chance
救回马托波总理
that prime minister Matobo will be recovered.
只要尚存一丝希望  我就绝不放弃
And while that chance exists,I'm not giving in.
史密斯上将  你的部队
Admiral Amith,your strike force
原地不动  继续保持战前准备状态
will remain in position and at full battle readiness.
明白  总统阁下
Yes,madam president.
总统阁下  你正在批准
Madam president,you're guaranteeing
对我们国家的另一次袭击
another attack on our country.
我们不会容忍勒索  乔  我们更不会被当成人质为他们利用
We will not be blackmailed,Joe,and we will not be held
这个国家从来不和恐怖分子谈判
hostage.This country does not negotiate with terrorists.
把这些话和那些死者家属说吧
Tell that to the families of the dead!
你有没有想过如果公众得知
Do you have any idea what the public reaction will be
这些恐怖袭击是由于你鲁莽的外交政策造成的
when word gets out that these are acts of terrorism?
他们会有什么样的反应
Brought about by your reckless foreign policy?
我敢保证你会受到弹劾的
I can guarantee there will be a call for your impeachment...
别说了  乔
That's enough,Joe.
我不能让这样的事情发生
I will not stand by and let this happen.
那你可以辞职了  乔
Then you can turn in your resignation,joe,
我是不会改变我的想法的
because I'm not changing my mind.
现在  要么坐下要么走人
Now sit down or leave.
对不起  总统阁下
I'm sorry,madam president.
你们好好想想你们正在做的事情
You people think about what you're doing here...
想想你们要为此付出多大的代价
about the precious you're willing to pay.
先生们
Gentlemen,
女士们  我明白你们当中很多人
Ladies I know that there are many of you here
同意国务卿史蒂文的看法
who agree with secretary Stevens.
如果我不能让你的疑惑减少
If I can't alleviate your doubts,
我至少可以让你明白我这么做的理由
I can at least help you to understand my reasonings.
当我宣誓就职的时候  我向我自己
When I took the oath of office,I swore to myself,
更向全体美国人民发誓  这个国家将继续
and to the american people,that this country would
作为这个世界的正义力量
continue to be a force for good in this world.
我们建国是基于我们的理想
We're a nation founded on ideals,
这些理想在今天正受到挑战
and those ideals are being challenged today.
我们对此的反应不但会影响我们这届政府
Now how we respond will not only define this
更会影响一代美国人民
administration,but an entire generation.
甚至包括桑加拉人民
And not just americans,but Sangalans,and anyone
还有那些希望从我们身上得到力量和指引的人们
else who looks to us for guidance and strength.
我不会令他们失望
I won't fail them...
你们也不会
and neither will you.
前面的道路很艰难
We're in for some tough times ahead.
让我们一起努力
Let's make sure we're ready.
谢谢大家
Thank you,everyone.
杰克
Hey,Jack.
他们在那儿  我要你放个追踪器在
They're over there. I want you to put a wire
马托波先生身上  快
on Mr. Matobo as fast as you can. Go.
你没事吧
You okay?
你说呢  杰克
What do you think,Jack?
你朝我开枪还把我活埋了
You shot me and buried me alive.
如果我们不那么做  你就会死在爱默生的手下了
If we hadn't,Emerson would have killed you.
很抱歉你必须继续隐藏起来
I'm sorry we had to keep you in the dark,
-我们别无选择  -不  你们有
- But we didn't have a choice.  - Yes,you did.
你可以选择相信我
You could have trusted me.
在联调局总部的时候如果我告诉你这一切
If I had told you everything back at the FBI,
你会信吗
Would you have believed me?
请坐  先生
Have a seat,please,sir.
那是什么
What's that?
这是个追踪器
It's a transmitter.
我会把它粘在你的一颗牙上
I'll be affixing it to one of your teeth.
这样我们就可以随时知道你的方位
We'll know exactly where you are at all times.
你就不再是孤身奋斗了
You won't be alone.
你是联调局的人吗
Are you with the FBI?
不  我只是一个家庭主妇
No,I'm a stay-at-home Mom.
张开你的嘴  谢谢
Open your mouth,please.
张大点
Wider.
谢谢
Good.
克罗伊进入了联邦调查局的服务器
Chloe accessed the FBI server.
杜马库在首都外围使两架
Dubaku brought down two planes
飞机坠毁了
just outside the capital.
超过270人因此丧命
Over 270 people were killed.
他威胁要杀死1万人
He's threatened to kill 10,000 more.
我们有不到一个小时的时间去阻止他
We have less than an hour to stop it.
尼科尔斯什么时候到
How long before Nichols gets here?
10分钟内
Ten minutes.
-你的耳机  -多谢
- Here's your com.  - Thanks.
你还好吧
You all right?
嗯  就是有点头晕
Yeah,just a little dizzy.
你找个座位坐下吧
You should take a seat.
我还好
I'm fine.
过来  坐下吧
Hey,come on. Take a seat.
这些都是真的吗
So it's really true?
是
Yeah.
我把我的生命都献给了调查局
I've devoted my life to the bureau
你却让我相信它已经腐败了
And you just expect me to believe that it's corrupted--
甚至整个政府都腐败了
that the entire government's been corrupted?
不是所有的人
Not all of them.
但直到我们查明之前
But until we find out who,
我们谁也不能相信
we can't trust anyone.
你认为你们四个人就可以搞得定吗
And the four of you really think you can stop this?
没有别的选择  道理就这么简单
We have to. It's as simple as that.
伊桑
Ethan...
借一步说话
Can we...?
总统完全是一意孤行
The president is completely alone on this,
如此下去  将有无数美国人丧生
And she's going to get a lot of Americans killed.
你得想办法说服她
You've got to find a way to talk some sense into her.
我们的观点一致  蒂姆
We're both on the same side here,Tim.
我需要你的帮助
And I'm going to need your help
才能改变她的想法
If we're going to change her mind.
你认为该怎么做
How do you propose we do that?
有一个人能说服她
There is someone she'll listen to.
我们也许能说服他帮我们
Maybe we can convince him to help us.
什么事
Go ahead.
她刚下车  正在上楼
I just dropped her off. She's on her way up.
好  在车里留意动静
Okay,stay in the car and keep watch.
结束后我打给你
I'll call you when it's done.
泰勒先生  你怎么进来的
Mr.Taylor,how did you get in here?
你派来的探员送我过来
Um... the agent you sent just brought me by to get
拿一些东西
a few of my things for...
泰勒先生  你没事吧
Mr.Taylor,are you all right?
泰勒先生  你还好吗
Mr.Taylor,are you okay?
泰勒先生  请告诉我你怎么了
Mr.Taylor,unless you tell me what's wrong,
否则我不知道
I don't know what...
救我  求你
Help me. Please.
卡宁先生
Yes,Mr. Kanin.
盖奇探员  我找亨利·泰勒
Agent Gedge,I'm looking for Henry Taylor.
他的手机无人接听  你在他身边吗
He's not answering his phone.Is he with you?
您现在无法与他通话  先生
You can't talk with him right now,sir.
为什么  他在哪
Why not? Where is he?
他在萨曼莎·罗斯的公寓和她谈话  先生
He's meeting with Samantha Roth in her apartment,sir.
为了什么
For what possible reason?
我不知道  先生  他没告诉我
I don't know,sir. He didn't tell me.
你为什么不守着他
Why aren't you with him?
泰勒先生坚持要单独会面  先生
Mr.Taylor insisted on meeting with her alone,sir.
我在车里  我就在屋外
I'm in the car.I'm just outside the building.
我才不管他坚持什么
I don't give a damn what he insisted.
我告诉过你  盖奇探员
We went through this,agent Gedge.
你不该让他们会面
You were supposed to keep him away from her.
你脑袋进水了吗
What the hell were you thinking?
非常抱歉  先生
I'm sorry,sir.
道歉没用
I'm not interested in your apology.
赶快把他叫出来
Just pull him out of there
让他马上打电话给我
And have him phone me as soon as possible.
别说话  先生
Don't try to speak,sir.
没什么好说的
There's nothing left to say.
我们在这等着
We will wait here.
好
All right.
他们来了
They're coming.
-辅助道路上驶来一辆车  -多少人
- One car from the service road. - How many people?
看不清  车窗贴了膜
I can't tell. The windows are tinted.
收到
Copy that.
最近怎么样  托尼
How are you doing,Tony?
还行
All right.
很高兴你能继续为我们工作
I was glad to hear you're still with us.
爱默生去哪了
Where's Emerson?
你今天见不到他了
You're not going to be dealing with him today.
什么意思
What do you mean?
他死了
He's dead.
利特法克和鲍尔也死了
So's Litvak and Bauer.
尸体在里屋  要不要打个招呼
I got them in a back room. You want to say hi?
你最好告诉我发生了什么事
You better start telling me what the hell is going on.
现在我做主了
I decided I'd rather not split the cut.
我不明白
I don't understand.
我认为你和艾默生是朋友
I thought you and emerson were friends
对  那是在他把我丢在联邦调查局之前
Yeah,that was before he left me to rot with the FBI.
你想不想要马托波
You want Matobo or not?
他在哪里
Where is he?
很近
Close.
我要见他和他老婆
I want to see him,and his wife.
钻石
Diamonds.
马托波
Matobo.
他在后车厢里
He's in the back of the truck.
确定没被跟踪后
Keep your tracks clean.
我们会给你打电话的
We might call on you again.
好的
Okay,then.
就这样算了
Let's put that behind us.
你得到你要的
You got what you want.
给我离开这里
Now,get the hell out of here.
滚
Now!
安全
Clear.
-克罗伊  -杰克  我收到信号了
-Chloe. -Jack,I've got him.
所有人准备出发
Get everyone ready to move out.
盖奇
Gedge...
Gedge.
别这样对我
Don't do this.
求你了
Please...
白宫还是不肯就范
The white house still has not complied.
美军还在原地集结虎视眈眈
American forces are still in position.
我认为这个总统不只是执迷不悟
I think this president is not just stubborn;
她是彻底疯了
She's insane.
你想怎么做
what do you intend to do?
当然是我们之前所承诺的
Exactly what we promised.
我们准备好了
We're ready,sir.
一会见
I'll see you in a moment.
目标在哪里
Where is the target located?
俄亥俄州的汲沦谷镇
Kidron,Ohio.
人口呢
Population?
3万
30,000.
目标设施位于
The processing facility is located
镇中心以西2公里处
two miles west of the town center.
伤亡会很大  大约一万八千
Casualties will be high,about 18,000.
开始吧
Begin.